touchdown.co.uk 2017-12-26

# Touchdown HolidaysPrivacy Policy

**Touchdown Holidays Website Privacy Policy**  

**Touchdown Holidays is a trading name of Travelbrands Limited.**

**Travelbrands Limited  **is a is a registered, bonded agency in London, England Reg. No. 5265964.

**Travelbrands Limited  **knows that you care how your personal information is collected and used. We have created this Site Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to do so reasonably and responsibly.

This Site Privacy Policy describes our personal information gathering and dissemination practices for Touchdown Holidays.

**What is Personal Information**  
Personal information is information about an identifiable individual. It includes your full name, address, telephone number, date of birth, email address, and any other information that identifies who you are or would allow someone to contact you. Personal information only becomes known to Travelbrands Limited when you provide it to us.

**Collection of Personal Information**  
Our Site uses various methods for you to request information about products and services. Contact information (like your e-mail address) is collected and used to send you information about our company, products, services or otherwise get in touch with you. Of course, you can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of our features. You may also choose not to receive e-mail from us: see the Accessing your Personal Information section below.

**Use of Personal Information**  
We use the information you provide us to perform the services for which such data was collected. For example, if you sign up for an e-mail newsletter, we will send the e-mail newsletter to the address you provide us. We also use the information you provide us for internal marketing purposes and for administration of the Site.

**How about children?**  
We do not wish to obtain personal information from children who are using our Sites unsupervised. Thus, we ask children to obtain the consent of their parent or guardian before providing us with any personal information.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**  
Travelbrands Limited does not sell your personal information to third parties and does not disclose your personal information except as may be required to process your request for travel services, such as cruises, hotels, resorts and tour bookings, or as required by law. In short, we don't share or sell our mailing list(s).

**Cookies?**  
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and connection capabilities so that our Site can provide you with the optimal user experience. The "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you are to receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, as cookies allow us to enhance your user experience, we recommend that you leave them turned on.

**How about third parties?**  
Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we use it responsibly. We employ or partner with other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include processing credit card payments and providing marketing assistance. These agents have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. We release personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law or protect the rights, property, or safety of Travelbrands Limited, its users, or others. Finally, in the unlikely event that Travelbrands Limited or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

**Security**  
We use industry-standard methods to protect your personal information from unauthorized access. Among other techniques, we usually store such information on a computer behind our "firewall" in a secure location, and we often restrict the number of employees internally who can access such data. Of course, there is no such thing as "perfect security" on the Internet. Further, please note that some of our services may be operated by a third party host, whose actions we do not control.

As discussed above, you can always choose not to provide certain information, even though it might be needed to take advantage of many of our features. Our Site also provides you with the opportunity to choose not to receive communications from us. You have the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided or requesting not to receive future communications:  
1\. You can modify your subscription at any time by clicking on Manage Account. You need to be logged in to see this option.  
2\. You can send an e-mail to [privacy@touchdown.co.uk](mailto:privacy@touchdown.co.uk)  
3\. You can send mail to the following postal address:  
Touchdown, Suite 5F, Gatwick House, Peeks Brook Lane, Horley, Surrey, RH6 9ST  
4\. You can call: 0800 619 0707

**Amendments**  
We may from time to time revise this policy by updating this posting. Amendments to this policy will be effective when posted. You should therefore periodically visit this page to review the current Site Privacy Policy, so you are aware of any such revisions to which you are bound.

These Sites may contain links to other sites. Travelbrands Limited is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

Policy Last Updated: July 5th, 2011
